### **Patrick Parreno**

24 Openbay Gardens Brampton, ON L6R 0V4 PatrickJParreno@gmail.com (Cell) 647.239.3342

Sunday, October 11<sup>th</sup>, 2020

ArcelorMittal Tailored Blanks 55 Confederation Pkwy Concord, ON L4K 4Y7

Dear Hiring Manager,

This letter expresses my interest in discussing the current open position of the IT Co-op position within your company. I can showcase my strong IT Skills, initiative, enthusiasm, collaborative and customer service skills. I believe that I will be of great benefit to your company.

I am a newly graduated student from George Brown College, previously enrolled in the Computer Programming Analyst program. As an academic student, I have taken part in both computer and business courses. I have gained experience in several software languages in these classes, including C#, Java, Angular, React, JavaScript/PHP, HTML, CSS and MySQL. The program also provided computer knowledge on assembling and configuring computer operating systems. The program requires dozens of projects where I have had to showcase my programming skills and computer software knowledge using the languages and skills I have learnt throughout the course. Additionally, I have gained knowledge and skills in business fundamentals such as; ethics, accounting, marketing and entrepreneurship.

During my most previous employment at the Classic Honda Dealership in Brampton, Ontario I was part of the technical department. As part of the team, I was responsible for assisting and troubleshooting staff with any technical issues as well as installing and configuring a variety of equipment. With this experience, I feel I can start contributing quickly at ArcelorMittal.

Attached is a copy of my resume for your review. I welcome the opportunity to discuss my qualifications with you in person. I can be reached at (647) 239-3342 or PatrickJParreno@gmail.com. Thank you for your time and consideration.

Sincerely,

Patrick Parreno

### **Patrick Parreno**

24 Openbay Gardens Brampton, ON L6R 0V41 Cell: (647)239-3342

PatrickJParreno@Gmail.com

# **Objective:**

Software Developer seeking opportunity to bring knowledge of engineering. networking, security and operating system software to the IT Co-op position with ArcelorMittal Tailored Blanks.

## **Qualifications:**

- Well trained in Advance Programming & Design skills
- Proficient in Web Content Management and data Retrieval
- Equipped with strong Collaborative Skills and great team based problem solving
- Multiple Project Management positions for different software based project
- Proficient and well versed in several different programming languages

### **Technical Skills**

•	Java	•	HTML	•	Angular	•	WordPress	•	Illustrator
•	Python	•	CSS	•	C#	•	Office 365	•	Sketch
•	React	•	Swift	•	MySQL	•	Photoshop	•	AdobeXD

### **Education:**

## George Brown College

September 2016 – August 2020

Advance Diploma in Computer Programming Analyst

- Built & Implemented Multiple projects with Java, Angular, React. C#, HTML/CSS, JavaScript and PHP, aiding in a development of knowledge along a variety of programming languages
- Developed Application within a team using Agile Methodologies, leading to good team based problem solving skills
- Developed databases using MySQL, ensure good base ideology for data retrieval

## **Professional Experience:**

### **Classic Honda**

April 2019 – September 2020

IT Assistant, Brampton ON

- Successfully put together and configured new desktop computers for colleague's
- Successfully installed Professional operating systems on a number of desktop computers as well as downloading and installing software off of department servers
- Helped colleague's troubleshoot and fix problematic computer software and printers

- Performed disaster recovery operations, including data back-ups
- Tested systems to ensure the elimination of bugs or viruses

#### Classic Honda

August 2017 – April 2019

Express Service Advisor, Brampton ON

- Implemented customer data into a database for easier access to customer files & records
- Detailed customer vehicles after maintenance services were completed, ensuring the vehicles were clean upon returning to the customer
- Drafted paperwork for customers receiving maintenance, resulting in technicians clearly knowing what area of the vehicle they will be working on
- Assisted in checking-in customers who had service appointments, leading to a steady flow in the work environment and making sure every customer was attended to

### **Cafe Demetres**

January 2017 – August 2017

Pastry Chef, Mississauga ON

- Prepared meals in a high volume kitchen with exceptional precision
- Organized and analyzed all inventory or goods and supplies, ensuring that everything was in stock and food supply was up to company standards
- In charge of ordering low in supply items from various vendors
- Ensured kitchen was cleaned and maintained, resulting in a clean work environment for all staff

# **NLS Logistics**

2016 (Seasonal; June – September)

General Labour, Mississauga ON

- Stocked and rotated products regularly, making sure all shelves were stocked with the appropriate items
- Arranged transportation of goods based on extracted information form database, ensuring clients received goods on the scheduled time
- Oversaw the arrival of new products, making sure they aligned with arrival time from database